Nitika Duggal



I am a dedicated and motivated Graduate Architect with a strong belief in the ability of Architecture to bring positive change in our society. Quality research combined with Design Thinking can be the vehicle which drives this change. I am backed with knowledge in using various software like Rhino 3D, ArchiCAD, AutoCAD, Revit, Adobe CC, and many more. I am more than adept to undertake the responsibilities as an Architecture Graduate. Problem-solving smartly and efficiently is what I do best.

OUALIFICATION

Architectural Journalism Licensed Architect in India

HOBBIES

Photography Architectural Journalism Hydroponics

EDUCATION

2017-2019: **Master of Architecture** University of Technology Sydney 2012-2017:

> **Bachelor of Architecture** University of Pune

+61 451 123 204



Graduate Of Architecture | Designer | Photographer

EXPERIENCE

July 2019 - June 2020 Graduate of Architecture

Ghazi Al Ali Architects, Sydney

Ghazi Al Ali Architects is a multi-disciplinary architectural and interior design practice During my tenure, I was guided by the Senior Architect while working on various projects, including high-density residential. My responsibilities included making Development Application (DA) drawings, documentation for Construction Certificate (CC) along with other documentation required in the field of Architecture. BIM software was heavily used throughout the tenure. I was also working closely with structural engineers, environmental engineers, and other contractors during the design phase of some of the projects.

2019 and 2020 Innovation Mentor

Humanitarian Innovation Hackathon, The Warren Center, Sydney

The brief was designed for students to work collaboratively in multi-discipline conceptualise practical solutions for real and current humanitarian issues that are identified by the humanitarian disaster organization RedR Australia in various parts of the world. My role as a mentor was to guide the students and help them in every step of the design thinking process to come up with novel and innovative solutions that would help alleviate the problems faced by the people of the region.

June 2016 -March 2017

Intern Architect

Ar. Hafeez Contractor, Mumbai

Architect Hafeez Contractor is one of the leading architectural firms in India. The firm takes into account the unique problems faced by that country. It caters to both national and international clients. I had the opportunity to work with one of the best master planning and design teams on housing and commercial projects ranging from 2-40 hectares. Throughout my internship, I engaged in many one-on-one sessions with Director Ar. Hafeez Contractor himself.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Graphisoft Archicad	Intermediate	Virtual Reality	Intermediate
Ps ————————————————————————————————————	Proficient	Adobe illustrator	Proficient
Id Adobe Indesign	Proficient	Autocad	Proficient
Revit	Intermediate	Sketchup	Intermediate
Rhino	Intermediate	Grasshopper	Intermediate
Navi Works	Intermediate	13 ——— Processing	Intermediate

REFERENCES

ANGELO CANDALEPAS: CANDLEPAS ASSOCIATES

info@candalepas.com.au +61(0)292837755

"Nitika demonstrated enthusiasm and excellent work ethic in her response to critical feedback, showing careful thought and making effective adjustments to her design within the strict schedule of assignment submissions."

JOAN VAN DE VEN: GHAZI AL ALI ARCHITECT

jo@ghazia.com 0424999414

"Nitika has proven herself to be an asset to the company. She has a positive attitude, always willing to help, and dedicated to the point of working overtime when required to meet critical deadlines. I have relied on her for various tasks from sending correspondence pertaining to project management such as DA consultant tenders, and working on DA's and CC's under my supervision. On a more personal level, although quiet, she has a positive influence on the culture of an office. She came in at a time of mass redundancies and the office atmosphere difficult to say the least and always kept a positive attitude as well as a good sense of humour."

AR HAFEEZ CONTRACTOR: AR HAFEEZ CONTRACTOR

hafeez@hcontractor.com (+9122) 22661920

"During this period Nitika has shown ability to understand concepts, work out details, draft design presentations and carry out office procedures. She has also developed skills in computer aided drawings."